{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Hester and Dimmesdale's child?",
      "answers": [
        "Sapphire",
        "Ruby",
        "Pearl",
        "Crystal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Governor's last name?",
      "answers": [
        "Bellingham",
        "Dimmesdale",
        "Chillingworth",
        "Wilson"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What letter is the Scarlet Letter?",
      "answers": [
        "B",
        "D",
        "C",
        "A"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Scarlet Letter stand for?",
      "answers": [
        "Awesome",
        "Adultery",
        "Attractive",
        "Ashamed"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What would Hester's punishment have been had she not had a child?",
      "answers": [
        "Death",
        "Jailed for life",
        "Exiled",
        "No Punishment"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What was Hester and Dimmesdale's plan for escaping?",
      "answers": [
        "Running to another town nearby",
        "Going to Europe on a pirate ship",
        "Confessing and being killed",
        "They had no plan to escape"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Roger Chillingworth is...",
      "answers": [
        "Not in the story",
        "A teacher at the school in town",
        "Dimmesdale's therapist",
        "Hester's husband"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Roger Chillingworth's real name?",
      "answers": [
        "John Doe",
        "Ben Sawyer",
        "Unknown",
        "Stephen James"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How many main characters are there?",
      "answers": [
        "3",
        "5",
        "4",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is Dimmesdale's Scarlet Letter?",
      "answers": [
        "Carved into his chest",
        "Sewed onto his clothes",
        "On his forehead",
        "Carved into his left palm"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ]
}
